<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Troubleshooter</string>
    <string name="wifi_instructions">Step 1: Open Settings\nStep 2: Select Connections\nStep 3: Select Wifi\nStep 4: Make sure that the wifi is switched on by toggling the button at the top right\nStep 5: Select the Wifi name that matches the one on premises\nStep 6: A popup may now appear asking for a Password, in this case enter the wifi password here. Most of the time this can be found either on the bottom of the router or on a magnet provided by the network owners internet service provider.\nStep 7: Hit connect and you’re done.</string>
    <string name="wifi_header">Connecting your phone to a home wifi connection is a great way to save data and often a good way to achieve better internet speeds. Provided that you have a Wifi connection at home or a friends house you can easily connect to this, here’s how: </string>
    <string name="out_of_space">Step 1: Delete any unneeded images or downloaded files that you may have on your phone. If you find that you are storing a lot of images on your phone, perhaps look into storing them on a cloud-based storage site, such as Google Drive.\nStep 2: Uninstall any unnecessary apps. Apps tend to take up a lot of room on a mobile device so if you aren’t using it, get rid of it! You can uninstall an app by pressing on it until a toolbar pops up with the option to uninstall.\nStep 3: If you cant do either, you may need to look into upgrading your phone to one with more storage.</string>
    <string name="out_of_space_header">Phones are great for many things but often run into issues with running out of space. Here are some tips to clear up space on your phone.</string>
    <string name="slow_phone_header">There is nothing more frustrating than when your phone runs unbearably slow. Here are some tips to assist with that.</string>
    <string name="slow_phone">Step 1: Close any unneeded apps. Closing out of an app does not actually close it on phones. On an android you have to press the three lines of the left hand of your phone to see all open apps, you can then swipe up to close them.\nStep 2: Clear space. If the phone is full, it will run slower as it has less space to work with. Try and clear some space out.\nStep 3: Restart the phone. Often, all you need is a good restart to refresh the phone.\nStep 4: Replace the phone. If none of the above helps, it may be time to replace the phone.</string>
    <string name="update_phone_header">Updating your phone is very important to ensure you stay safe and secure while using it. Here is how.</string>
    <string name="update_phone">Step 1: Open Settings.\nStep 2: Select ‘About Phone’.\nStep 3: Tap ‘Check for Updates’. If there is an update available, a button will appear with the update. Click on that button.\nStep 4: Press install. The update will now install.\nThe amount of time it takes for an update to install can vary on the size of the update, we recommend making sure your phone stays charged and has an internet connection throughout the process. If it does not, the update will fail.</string>
    <string name="bad_battery">Step 1: Close any unneeded apps. Closing out of an app does not actually close it on phones. On an android you have to press the three lines of the left hand of your phone to see all open apps, you can then swipe up to close them./nStep 2: Put the phone into power-saving mode. In order to find this setting, going into your settings app and search ‘Power Saving Mode’. A page should come up in which you can turn on Power saving mode. This will help to make your battery last longer./nStep 3: Avoid overcharging. Where possible, you should avoid letting your phone run to 0% or charging to 100%. This stresses the battery out and reduces its capacity.\nStep 4: Replace the phone. As phones get older, the battery begins to fail. If you find your phone is not lasting very long before it needs a charge, it may be time to replace it. </string>
    <string name="bad_battery_header">Poor battery life can be extremely frustrating and can cause you to be a "wall hugger", here are a few steps to combat it:</string>
    <string name="bluetooth">Step 1: Open Settings. /nStep 2: Select Connections. /nStep 3: Select Bluetooth. \nStep 4: Make sure that bluetooth is enabled by toggling the slider at the top right of the page. /nStep 5: Select the device name that you wish to pair with (you may need to set the target device into pairing mode for it to appear here). /nStep 6:Most devices will now present a pin code, confirm that this matches on your phone if not enter the correct pin and hit connect.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_header">Bluetooth is a great way to connect to your bluetooth compatible devices over a short range, this might be to stream music, take calls or simply provide some form of phone control over a particular device. Connecting to bluetooth devices couldn’t be simpler, heres how to connect to a device.</string>
    <string name="suspicious_messages">Step 1: They are trying to get access to your phone/computer. Anyone trying to remotely access your device that isn’t someone you have called asking for help is likely a hacker attempting to gain access to your device.\nStep 2: They are asking for you to purchase items. Most banks/corporations will not contact you via phone and demand payment. It is especially dangerous if they are asking you to purchase gift cards.\nStep 3: They are asking for personal information. If someone you don’t know is inquiring for personal information, they may be a hacker attempting to gain information about you. Be very careful with what information you give out.</string>
    <string name="suspicious_messages_2">\nStep 4: They are aggressive and rude. Most hackers will attempt to use aggression and threats to try and coerce you into giving the information they need/doing the things they need you to do. Any true customer support member will be polite over the phone.\n Step 5: You are not expecting contact from them. If someone you don’t know calls/messages you out of the blue and you are not expecting them, take extra care when communicating with them.</string>
    <string name="suspicious_messages_header">The world is full of people trying to access your money/information illegally. Here are some handy things to look out for to let you know if someone is suspicious!</string>
</resources>